YOAV TZIPORI

CYBER SECURITY ANALYST

yoavtzipori12@gmail.com Tel Aviv Isreal 0544401585 Dec, 1999 — Israel & French http://linkedin.com/in/yoav-tzipori

OBJECTIVE

I am a former Israeli commando soldier with a passion for cybersecurity and ethical hacking.

With experience in ethical hacking, I have completed over 500 hours of hands-on courses and obtained numerous certificates.

I have also developed my hacking and scanning tools using Python, showcasing my proficiency in hacking, vulnerability assessment,

web penetration testing, mobile security, and other aspects of the field

SKILLS

Web PT /mobile
Virtualization vmware/VB
Mac/Linux/Windows-os
python , java , JS , html , css
ethical Hacking / cyber Defence
Technical writing
Implement security features
darak web / Tor / vpn / proxy chain
Networking/protocols/routers/switch
es
ability to multitasking

LANGUAGES

English | Advanced Hebrew | Native

EXPERIENCE

Technical Writer

Nov 2022 - Feb 2023

Decision Point - Boston Massachusetts

Constructed Standard Operating Procedures for major cybersecurity and technical initiatives that improved adherence to industry security and compliance standards.

Structured and designed a template for technical writing throughout the organization using various Microsoft Office products.

Inventory Manager

Mar 2022 — Sep 2022

dent wizard - ST.Louis Missouri

Managed the inventory of a large corporate in the state, recording and updating inventory data.

Removed unsalable items and coordinated stock distribution to various sites.

Updated and maintained inventory on Excel sheets.

EDUCATION

Cyber security

Dec 2022 - Jul 2023

HackerU - tel aviv

-Platform elevation of Privilege,web application ,Advanced Infrastructure Attacks,Windows server ,python programming language,Linux ,networking ,web Application penetration Tasting,Cyber infrastructures ,Mobil Penetration Tasting

SIEM-SOC & introduction to Malware Analysis

TDX-arena practical Exam

computer science

Mar 2023 - Present

the open university of israel - tel aviv

≘ CERTIFICATIONS & COURSES

CEH ethical hacking

CCNA cisco Networking

web PT - ThriveDX

Cisco IT Essentials